# **Frontend Developer**

# Atakere Kester Williams

#### Objective

I'm a Frontend & Mobile-app developer, based in Lagos - Nigeria and I have been developing for more than three years. During this period I have worked on several projects while learning multiple web languages that I now speak fluently and confidently backed by the experiences I have garnered over the years. I currently learn new, in-demand web technologies to improve my backend skills on my journey to Fullstack status.

#### **Experience**

August 2018

#### **Started Frontend Development**

Started my web development journey set on the goal of making Web Development more known as a transformational and profitable skill through my works and impact in the development community in Nigeria and the World at large.

June 2020 - Current

#### Freelance Frontend developer

I offer web development services that put business in the right spot socially; getting across to the right customers and easily accessible by many.

August 2020 - Current

#### Mobile Development

I started mobile development using React Native in building an app called Self which is an all-in-one app for Android and iOS users. This project is still in development.

#### Portfolios thealphaknight.com

#### Education

April 2018 - April 2022

BSc. Elect/Elect Engineering

Obafemi Awolowo University

### **Skills**

HTML5 CSS3/SCSS

JAVASCRIPT TYPESCRIPT

REACT NEXT JS

REACT NATIVE THREE JS

VUE JS GIT(HUB)

#### **Interests**

I enjoy watching movies, listening to music and eating.

## **Contact**

- atakerewilliams
- codergon
- atakere\_williams